

FULL STACK REACT DEVELOPER

#### **Personal Details**

Málaga

Spain

+34 633 546 175

<u>castillamariscal.juan@gmail.com</u> <u>contact@johndev.dev</u>

## Links

Porfolio Web

**Customers** websites

#### Skills

**Problem Solving** 

Creativity

Commitment

Adaptability

Responsible

Teamwork

Puntuality

Leadership

Self-taught

Persistent and very resilient

Critical thinking

Attention to detail

#### Stack

Java

HTML, CSS, JS

React, Next, Astro, Vite, Remix

Php, Laravel

DataBase, MySql

Tailwind, Bootstrap

Wordpress, Shopify

MVC, Clean Code

Git, Bitbucket

Scrum and agile methodology

Ddev

## **Profile**

Fullstack web developer with +3 years of experience. I have knowledge in digital marketing, seo, specialized in React, PHP and flexible profile to learn and adapt to new technologies. Noted for creating sites that exceed expectations. Perseverance and flexibility as main qualities.

# **Employment History**

## Web Developer, Prodigia Consultores S.L, Málaga

MARCH 2023 - PRESENT

- Maintenance and troubleshooting of websites and online stores.
- Working with web development companies in the e-commerce sector.
- Performance improvements in websites.
- Design Thinking methodology application

### Freelance Web Developer, Freelance, Online

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

- Complete website development and publishing in Google Sites.
- Adapting websites to the client's needs
- You can find my projects on Behance.
- Troubleshooting websites clients problems and enhance sites performance

### Private Class Teacher, Superprof, Online

JULY 2021 - AUGUST 2022

I teach PHP, HTML5, CSS and JS at the higher level of Vocational Training. 95% statisfied students.

## **Education**

#### Web App Development, Cenec Málaga, Málaga

SEPTEMBER 2021 - MARCH 2023

- Advanced course in web application development.
- Graduated with one of the best academic records.
- I learned programming in Java, PHP, Laravel and Python.

### A.S.I.R, I.E.S. Oretania, Linares

SEPTEMBER 2019 - DECEMBER 2021

- Computer systems and network administration.
- Learn systems, networks and PHP programming

### 2, Seville Univerity, Seville

SEPTEMBER 2016 - JUNE 2018

• 2 years of career as a computer engineer

#### Courses

## Complete JS Course, Udemy

AUGUST 2021 - MAY 2022

# React Mern Hooks Complete Guide, Udemy

AUGUST 2023 - PRESENT

#### Master in PHP, Udemy

NOVEMBER 2020 - NOVEMBER 2021

## Languages

## **English**